my name is Dmytro general fine the city
我的名字叫迪米特罗将军城
of JetBrains and I've been involved with
我参与了JetBrains的工作
the intelligent platform probably from
智能平台可能来自
the very beginning of its existence as a
它作为一个存在的开始
separate entity and today I'm going to
独立的实体，今天我要去
tell to talk a little bit about how you
告诉我谈谈你的情况
can as plug-in developers or product
可以作为插件开发人员或产品
developers can leverage IntelliJ
开发人员可以利用IntelliJ
platform to build your own stuff and
建立自己的东西的平台
maybe even sell it and earn a lot of
甚至卖掉它并赚很多
money doing that so first of all what
钱，所以首先
isn't a intelligent platform intelligent
不是一个智能平台
that form is actually the foundation of
这种形式实际上是
all of the ideas that we have built so
我们建立的所有想法
it was extracted from the IntelliJ IDEA
它是从IntelliJ IDEA中提取的
IDE and made more general and refactored
IDE，并变得更加通用和重构
and now it's building block for not just
现在，它不仅为
our IDs but also some other tools and
我们的ID，还有其他一些工具，
it's a completely open source and free
这是一个完全开源和免费的
and available on the Apache 2 license so
并在Apache 2许可证上可用，因此
you can use it for essentially any kind
您基本上可以将其用于任何种类
of element yourself so first of all
元素本身，所以首先
we'll look at how we use IntelliJ
我们将看看我们如何使用IntelliJ
platform in our products and it may be
产品中的平台，可能是
actually more you may find out something
实际上，您可能会发现一些东西
new it's probably more than we were
新的可能比我们更多
using so as I mentioned the internship
就像我提到的实习
platform began as part as part of the
平台开始作为
IntelliJ IDEA codebase and actually the
IntelliJ IDEA代码库，实际上是
first version of the ID did not have any
该ID的第一个版本没有任何
any plug-in API and then gradually we
任何插件API，然后逐步
made it more flexible and more
使它更加灵活和更多
extensible and at extension points in
可扩展并在
modularized it and so on and so forth
对其进行模块化等等
and if someone is interested in how we
如果有人对我们的方式感兴趣
went about it I'm going to give a
为此，我要给
presentation on it to if that jetbrains
关于它的介绍
day in Malmo in on September 7th so
9月7日在马尔默的一天
there's a link over there that you can
那里有一个链接，您可以
use to register if you're interested and
用于注册，如果你有兴趣和
I hope to get those recorded and
我希望得到那些记录并
published online later now there are all
现在在网上发布，现在有
the small IDs that we have built on top
我们在顶部建立的小ID
of the platform so by John Ruby mine and
约翰·露比（John Ruby）和
all the others there's the C++ ID that
其他所有的C ++ ID
we have recently announced that we are
我们最近宣布我们
right now working on there is one more
现在正在努力
idea that we haven't announced yet
我们尚未宣布的想法
but we are also working on it and so
但我们也在努力
stay tuned for further announcements I
请继续关注我的进一步公告
guess and what these products actually
猜猜这些产品到底是什么
are are it's mostly essentially a reaper
基本上是收割者吗
distribution of the platform which
该平台的分布
removes the stuff that is not needed for
删除不需要的东西
a bit
一点点
our ID that bundles the plug in that is
我们将插件捆绑在一起的ID是
relevant for the market that we're
与我们所处的市场相关
talking about our charm bundles a
谈论我们的魅力捆绑
bicycle plug-in will be mine vitals the
自行车插件将成为我的生命力所在
Ruby plug-in and so on and be customize
Ruby插件等并进行自定义
the UI to make it the most relevant and
使其最相关的用户界面
most applicable for the target audience
最适用于目标受众
from stuff like new product creation
从诸如新产品创建之类的东西
project setup interpreter configuration
项目设置解释器配置
so on it is custom in the ideas and
所以在想法上是习惯
different from how tools in IntelliJ
与IntelliJ中的工具不同
IDEA ultimate and technically they all
IDEA终极技术上都
live in the same source three years
住在同一来源三年
IntelliJ IDEA itself so this makes the
IntelliJ IDEA本身，这使得
whole integration story much easier for
整个整合的故事要容易得多
us but that's not all of it so the
我们，但还不是全部，所以
IntelliJ IDEA platform is also used as
IntelliJ IDEA平台也用作
part of NBS for those of you who are not
国家统计局的一部分
familiar with NPS it's it's it stands
熟悉NPS就是这样
for meta programming system and it's
用于元编程系统，它是
essentially something that we call the
本质上我们称之为
DSL workbench so this is a tool that
DSL工作台，所以这是一个工具
lets you define your own dear
让您定义自己的亲爱的
domain-specific languages it gives you
它为您提供了特定领域的语言
for free essentially the idea
本质上是免费的
functionality for those two main
这两个主要功能
specific languages and you can also
特定语言，您还可以
specify how the idea cells get generated
指定想法单元格的生成方式
into something such as Java code or C
变成Java代码或C之类的东西
code the JavaScript code or whatever it
编写JavaScript代码或其他代码
is a target language and this has a
是目标语言，它具有
number of interesting uses and MPs
有趣的用途和MP的数量
actually uses the UI framework of
实际使用的UI框架
IntelliJ IDEA but it does not use most
IntelliJ IDEA，但它不使用大多数
of the code centric features that make
以代码为中心的功能
the IntelliJ IDEA platform so
IntelliJ IDEA平台
interesting actually
其实很有趣
so you took place it does not use any
所以你发生了它不使用任何
text editors just replaces all of this
文本编辑器仅替换所有这些
with its own dsl oriented editing framer
带有自己的面向DSL的编辑成帧器
another piece of code that uses the
另一段使用
internship framework is actually the
实习框架实际上是
content compiler so constantly as you
像您一样不断地进行内容编译
probably know it's a programming
可能知道这是一个编程
language it is that we are developing an
语言是我们正在开发
JetBrains
JetBrains
and of course we wanted to reuse the
当然，我们想重用
same code base for the compiler itself
编译器本身的相同代码库
and for the 8lg plugin and in order to
而对于8lg插件，为了
be able to do that we actually extracted
能够做到这一点，我们实际上提取
a small part of the IntelliJ IDEA in
IntelliJ IDEA中的一小部分
Tunisia platform just the poor
突尼斯平台只是穷人
psi stuff Java psi and overall parse
psi内容Java psi和整体解析
indexing logic and packages there's a
索引逻辑和程序包有一个
separate jar and made use of it in the
单独的罐子并在其中使用
cotton compiler and it's actually fairly
棉花编译器，实际上相当
small so the distribution of the cost
小所以成本分配
and compiler just
和编译器只是
over seven megabytes compared to I don't
超过7兆字节，而我没有
know 200 megabytes of the Internet JD
知道200兆字节的Internet JD
ultimate it's quite a big difference and
最终，这是一个很大的不同，
see so the prod products beta based on
看到所以prod产品beta基于
the intelligent platform can also be a
智能平台也可以是
bit lightweight another thing is
轻巧的另一件事是
something called up source which I guess
我猜是所谓的来源
not that many people know about we
没有多少人知道我们
announced it recently and it's right now
最近宣布，现在
it's more of a prototype than an actual
它更多的是原型而不是实际的
product but it's actually a very
产品，但实际上是一个非常
interesting one so I'm going to show a
有趣的一个，所以我将展示一个
little bit of this right now so
现在一点点这样
essentially the app source is a
本质上，应用程序源是
web-based source code browser and right
基于Web的源代码浏览器和正确的
now it's sure you can go to absorb
现在确定您可以吸收
acecomm it's public it's not something
acecomm是公开的，不是什么
that you can use for your or your own
您可以将其用于自己或自己的
project but you can use it for browsing
项目，但您可以使用它进行浏览
the source of IntelliJ IDEA Community
IntelliJ IDEA社区的来源
Edition source code and you can see that
版源代码，您可以看到
it gives you okay for some reason it
由于某种原因，它可以使您满意
does not give anything useful so
没有提供任何有用的信息
actually it's supposed to be like real
实际上应该是真实的
code editor with syntax highlighting and
带有语法高亮显示的代码编辑器和
go-to declaration stuff like that but it
像这样去声明的东西，但是它
looks like something is broken with app
应用似乎坏了
source okay nevermind it's supposed to
来源好吧，没关系，它应该
be very nice but today it doesn't work
非常好，但是今天不起作用
at least it shows you the tips and and
至少它向您显示了提示和
other nice stuff but we do have some CR
其他不错的东西，但我们确实有一些CR
okay so now probably did not completely
好吧，所以现在可能没有完全
index a new revision so in the older
为新修订版本编制索引，以便在较旧的版本中
version you actually see how the older
您实际上看到的版本较旧
navigation features works you can just
导航功能可以使您
press go to Declaration you can view the
按进入宣言，您可以查看
documentation you can jump to
您可以跳转到的文档
implementations of stuff so for example
东西的实现，例如
look at all the PSI element
看所有的PSI元素
implementations and this or it will take
实现，这或将需要
take a while to load all of them but
花一些时间来加载所有
yeah you see that shows some of the
是的，您看到了一些
results and actually under the hood this
结果，实际上是在幕后
is also running into the running it
也正在运行中
slimmed down version of the intelligent
精简版智能
platform so we have so we have ears
平台，所以我们有，所以我们有耳朵
obviously does not have any of this
显然没有任何
video either as part of the intelligent
视频作为智能的一部分
platform budget users or the same part
平台预算用户或同一部分
of the same
一样的
or deciphering with the cousin compiler
或与堂兄弟编译器一起解密
also uses and its adds extra chunks such
也使用并增加了额外的块
as indexing and project model and
作为索引和项目模型，以及
interoperability and stuff like that and
互操作性之类的东西，以及
right now I suppose Java but we are also
现在我想是Java，但我们也是
planning to add other languages such as
计划添加其他语言，例如
XML and JavaScript in the very in the
XML和JavaScript在
very near future so that's essentially
不久的将来，这基本上是
how we use Intel chip framework
我们如何使用英特尔芯片框架
internally beyond internal users there
内部超越内部用户
are also a number of external products
也是一些外部产品
that are already that already exist that
已经存在的那个
are abused on the intelligent lifeform
在智能生活中被滥用
the list is not as long as we want it to
列表不长，只要我们想要
be and that's actually why we are
是的，这实际上就是我们为什么
holding this webinar to tell more people
举行此网络研讨会以告诉更多人
about how the intelligent idea platform
关于智能创意平台如何
can be used and how you can build your
可以使用以及如何建立自己的
own tools on top of that so the big one
最重要的是拥有自己的工具
is obviously Android studio which was an
显然是Android Studio
announced at by Google at the Google i/o
由Google在Google I / O上宣布
conference a couple of months ago it's
几个月前的会议
not really a very good example of the
并不是一个很好的例子
platform usage because it's it's an idea
平台使用，因为这是一个主意
which is primarily it's a repackaged
主要是重新包装
version of IntelliJ IDEA Community
IntelliJ IDEA社区的版本
Edition so there is not that much new
版，因此没有太多新内容
new development made by Google that
Google的新开发成果
makes it different from it is JTA
使它与JTA不同
Community Edition itself so there is a
社区版本身，所以有一个
certain amount of new development that
一定数量的新发展
they did they have a custom UI for the
他们是否有一个自定义的用户界面
Gradle based product model and they
基于Gradle的产品模型及其
customized some stuff to work the way
定制一些东西以工作方式
they want it and obviously they have
他们想要它，显然他们有
their own branding but all in all it's
自己的品牌，但总而言之
not like a full-blown separate product
不像成熟的独立产品
is very very near to what we did with
非常接近我们所做的
IntelliJ IDEA Community Edition and by
IntelliJ IDEA社区版和
the way it was developed completely in
它完全被开发出来的方式
partnership with us so we have even a
与我们建立合作伙伴关系，因此我们甚至拥有
lot of help to Google guys and we are
对Google员工有很多帮助，我们
very excited about how this all turned
一切都变得非常激动
out and so on another user of our
等等，我们的另一个用户
products is a company called called
产品叫一家公司
guide wire and you probably have not
导丝，您可能还没有
heard of it because it's not a developer
听说过，因为它不是开发人员
company at all it's a company for
公司完全是为了
building software for insurance
保险构建软件
companies to let essentially for
基本上允许的公司
calculating how how much of an inch
计算多少英寸
response the insurance is how
应对保险是如何
expensively your insurance policy is
昂贵地，您的保险单是
going to be
将
and they have their own programming
他们有自己的编程
language JVM programming language called
语言JVM编程语言称为
gosu and they are using it essentially
gosu，他们基本上在使用它
to give the users of their products
给产品的用户
tools program they're the oldest
工具程序，它们是最古老的
environment and they have built an idea
环境，他们已经建立了一个想法
for a ghost programming language on top
在顶部使用幽灵编程语言
of IntelliJ IDEA and they have built
IntelliJ IDEA，他们已经建立
also a lot of custom UI for the
也有很多自定义的用户界面
domain-specific sub that they are doing
他们正在执行的特定于域的子
and it's not yet released but is going
它尚未发布但正在
to be released fairly soon and we've
即将发布，我们已经
also have been in touch with them and
也一直与他们保持联系
they seem to be quite happy with the
他们似乎对
experience that they've had the Left row
经历过左排
that I would like to mention is
我想说的是
something called and better it's a
叫做更好的东西是
fairly new thing it's a it's an open
相当新的东西，这是开放的
source tool which is based on MPs and it
基于MPs的源工具
targets MPs for the development of
针对国会议员的发展
embedded software as if it probably
嵌入式软件，好像
guess from the name so if when you want
从名字猜测，所以如果你想
to write software for I don't know your
为我不知道你写软件
fridge or something like that you can
冰箱或类似的东西，你可以
which has a microcontroller embedded in
内嵌微控制器
it you can actually use embedded to
您实际上可以使用嵌入式
write it in a nice graphical high-level
用漂亮的图形化高级语言编写
way and then generate a low-level C code
然后生成一个低级的C代码
that will get compiled by the platform
将由平台编译
compiler on the device so you can check
设备上的编译器，因此您可以检查
out the blog here if you interested in
如果您对此感兴趣，请在此处发布博客
more details and I don't know how much
更多细节，我不知道多少
about use of this tool but it's we see
关于该工具的使用，但我们看到了
this as a very exciting intervention a
这是一个非常令人兴奋的干预
couple of more projects that I'm going
我要去的几个其他项目
to show now are no longer in active
现在显示不再有效
development by still there are also to
发展依旧还有
some degree success stories of beauty
一定程度的美丽成功故事
attains AG platform so the first one was
获得AG平台，所以第一个是
by a Swedish company called es n dot M e
由一家名为es n dot M e的瑞典公司提供
and this company has built a web
这家公司已经建立了一个网站
framework for real-time web development
实时Web开发框架
in Python so their target market was
在Python中，因此他们的目标市场是
mostly game developers and they are
主要是游戏开发商，他们是
actually used in the Battlefield series
实际用于《战地风云》系列
of games and they have built they're
游戏，他们建立了他们
actually very nice framework and very
实际上非常好的框架
nice tools for this framework on top of
此框架之上的好工具
biochar and solution it was a plugin and
biochar和解决方案，它是一个插件，
then they packaged it as a separate IDE
然后他们将其打包为单独的IDE
and distributed it to their cost
并分配给他们的成本
unfortunately they were acquired by
不幸的是，他们被
Electronic Arts and so they are no
电子艺术，所以他们不是
longer providing support for this as a
不再为此提供支持
separate company and so I guess it's the
独立的公司，所以我想这是
tool is no longer publicly available and
该工具不再公开可用，并且
a product is something called real Ixia
产品就是真正的Ixia
this was an actions and ID for
这是一个动作和ID
ActionScript which is B which was also
ActionScript是B，也是
based on NBS so they have built the
基于NBS，因此他们建立了
generators from from them so they built
来自他们的发电机，所以他们建造了
a DSL that mineral the structure of
DSL结构的DSL
ActionScript and they build generators
ActionScript并生成生成器
to the action actual action script
到动作实际动作脚本
language and they had a fairly nice user
语言，他们有一个相当不错的用户
experience it was a commercial tool but
经历过它是一种商业工具，但是
it wasn't so I believe it never actually
并非如此，我相信从来没有
reached the 1.0 release development
达到了1.0版本的开发
seized in the year 2010 and yeah now the
在2010年查获，是的，现在
color the website contains something
为网站包含颜色
called is a different not related to
被称为是不相关的
ActionScript in any way so haven't told
尚未告知ActionScript
it we haven't talked about how people
我们还没有谈论人们如何
are actually using the intuitive idea
实际上是在使用直观的想法
platform now let's look at some of the
平台，现在让我们看一些
companies that are inside it so you give
里面的公司，所以你给
a brief overview of the main modules
主要模块的简要概述
that comprise the energy platform you
组成您的能源平台
can actually look at the source code for
可以实际查看源代码
it so under the community directory
在社区目录下
there is platform and here are some of
有平台，这里有一些
the modules that I'm going to be talking
我要讲的模块
about or platform and stuff like that so
关于或平台之类的东西
it's all there you can just look at the
就在那里，您可以看看
source code and see how it all fits
源代码，看看它们如何适合
together
一起
so the first module I like to mention is
所以我要提到的第一个模块是
the core module it's actually the low
核心模块实际上是低端
the most lower-level part of the
最底层的部分
platform it contains the virtual file
平台包含虚拟文件
system implementation code contains the
系统实施代码包含
low the general language support
一般语言支持低
features such as lexing parsing psi
Lexing解析psi等功能
structure references and so on and so
结构参考等等
forth and it contains some utility
并包含一些实用程序
classes for multi-threading collections
多线程集合的类
we have essentially our really written
我们基本上已经写了
version of guava and so on and so forth
番石榴的版本等等
it does not have any dependencies it
它没有任何依赖关系
does not have any support for specific
没有针对特定内容的任何支持
languages but it's just like the most
语言，但就像大多数
basic building block on top of which you
在其之上的基本构建块
can build a compiler or the ID or s
可以构建一个编译器或ID或s
command line the nicest tool or
命令行最好的工具或
something like that and that's actually
这样的东西，实际上
the part which is used by the cosmetic
化妆品使用的部分
compiler the next module is nothing
编译器下一个模块什么都没有
called platform the platform contains
平台包含的称为平台
actually most of the UI stuff that we
实际上，我们大部分的UI内容
have so it contains the action system
有它包含动作系统
which lets you put together toolbars and
让您将工具栏和
menu items and buttons and stuff like
菜单项和按钮之类的东西
that it contains most of our UI
它包含了我们大部分的用户界面
framework to minos dialogues fancy lease
minos对话框架租赁
tables reviews all of that stuff pop-ups
表格会查看所有这些弹出式窗口
we have a lot of it also has our text
我们有很多它也有我们的文字
editor implementation and it has also to
编辑器实现，它还必须
the UI for for the gift view the next
礼物的用户界面查看下一个
module is something called LAN and this
模块是所谓的局域网，这
contains the foundation for that case
包含该案的基础
contains the basic implementations for
包含的基本实现
our code inside features and the way we
我们的代码内部功能以及我们的方式
do stuff is actually we do stuff in this
做事情实际上是我们在做事情
area is actually quite different from
面积实际上与
some of the other IDs so when we build
其他一些ID，因此当我们构建时
some refactorings or code navigation
一些重构或代码导航
features we try to make them as general
我们试图使它们成为通用的功能
as possible so we extract the
尽可能地提取
language-independent part and we put it
语言无关的部分，我们把它
into the lang module so that everyone
进入lang模块，以便每个人
can use it and then we build specific
可以使用它，然后我们建立特定的
implementations on in specific languages
以特定语言实现
where for example the Java or the Python
例如Java或Python
module contains only the part that is
模块仅包含以下部分
specific for implementing this feature
专门用于实现此功能
for this language and what this means is
对于这种语言，这意味着
there it is that by writing a small
就是通过写一个小
amount of code you can leverage a huge
您可以利用大量的代码
amount of code that we have built in the
我们在其中构建的大量代码
platform you can get a lot of very
平台，您可以得到很多
powerful code editing features for very
强大的代码编辑功能，非常
little effort so you have some of the
一点点的努力，所以你有一些
features that are there like
那里的功能
highlighting a navigation completion
突出显示导航完成
refactor is good for matter the other
重构对其他事情有好处
sort of stop there and if you are able
有点停在那里，如果你有能力
to leverage this stuff for your project
为您的项目利用这些东西
and you it's it's actually the way to
你就是这实际上是
get the biggest benefit of out the
得到最大的好处
IntelliJ platform so there is a bunch of
IntelliJ平台，所以有一堆
other stuff there the local history
当地历史上的其他东西
modulus part of the platform so we
平台的模数部分，所以我们
automatically keep track of all the
自动跟踪所有
changes
变化
to files ability the minutes if this
分钟的文件能力，如果这
feature saves a lot of users Dimond
功能节省了很多用户戴蒙德
saves a lot of being very often we have
节省了很多我们经常拥有的
a general favor for building debuggers
对构建调试器的普遍青睐
which is obviously used by our who by
这显然是由我们的人使用的
all of the ideas that we have we have a
我们拥有的所有想法都有
test runner framework which is based on
基于的测试运行器框架
top of team city service messages and
团队城市服务消息的顶部和
it's very easy to write an adapter for a
为一个适配器编写适配器非常容易
custom test ring or to plug it in with
定制测试环或将其插入
the test runner and to get your green
测试跑步者并获得果岭
red bar and destination stuff like that
红色酒吧和类似目的地的东西
for any test framer that you have in
对于您拥有的任何测试成帧器
your custom language we also have a
您的自定义语言，我们还有一个
general version control system
通用版本控制系统
integration framework so if you need any
集成框架，因此如果需要
kinda version at all integration can
有点集成的版本可以
take our VCS framework and you can take
采用我们的VCS框架，您可以采用
our plugins for supporting specific
我们的插件支持特定
version control systems and your users
版本控制系统和您的用户
are going to get a great experience with
将获得很好的经验
version control without now I'm going to
没有现在的版本控制，我要去
talk about some of the modules that are
谈论一些模块
not strictly speaking part of the
不严格地说是
IntelliJ IDEA platform they belong more
他们更多地属于IntelliJ IDEA平台
properly to the IntelliJ IDEA Community
正确地进入IntelliJ IDEA社区
Edition source product but they're they
版源产品，但他们是
are still very useful pieces of
仍然是非常有用的
functionality then that you can use in
然后可以在其中使用的功能
your project if you need them so the
您的项目，如果您需要它们，那么
first one is Java psi and there are p
第一个是Java psi，有p
assigns essentially as it says here it's
基本上按照这里所说的进行分配
a URL as part of our java support so it
URL作为我们Java支持的一部分，因此
does parsing for java does reference
不会为Java进行解析吗？
resolution it does code analysis
解析代码解析
essentially it does not do code
本质上它不做代码
completion because code completion is
完成，因为代码完成是
not something that you need a standalone
不是你需要一个独立的东西
tool list it's an interactive feature
工具列表，它是一个交互式功能
but if you are building if you want to
但是如果您要建造的话
build for example a standalone code
构建例如独立代码
analysis tool something similar to find
分析工具类似的东西
parts of check style you can take you
支票样式的一部分，您可以带您
can take the core part and determine psi
可以作为核心部分并确定psi
part and we get a very lightweight
部分，我们得到了非常轻巧的
subset of the IntelliJ IDEA munitions
IntelliJ IDEA弹药的子集
community of a different source code and
不同源代码的社区，以及
essentially use it for building your own
本质上用它来构建自己的
tool and get a lot of stuff done by us
工具，并由我们完成很多工作
for free and the cotton compiler uses
免费，棉花编译器使用
that as well by the way so it can parse
顺便说一句，以便它可以解析
Java class files and Java source files
Java类文件和Java源文件
using the Java psi modules so that you
使用Java psi模块，以便您
can get
可以得到
scroll sign you should drop it because
滚动符号，应将其删除，因为
encode in Java code then we have a lot
用Java代码编码，那么我们有很多
of support for XML it goes into all of
对XML的支持涉及到所有
our products not just intelligent
我们的产品不仅智能
Edition and we do a lot of SAP there so
版本，我们在那里有很多SAP，因此
obviously we do parsing reduce a lot of
显然，我们进行解析会减少很多
schema support schema validation and
模式支持模式验证和
completion based on schemas where
根据模式完成
schemas can be DTD or xml schema or
模式可以是DTD或xml模式，也可以是
relax ng also very common task is when
放松也是很常见的任务是什么时候
different frameworks have xml based
不同的框架都基于xml
configuration files i don't know the
我不知道的配置文件
spring beans for example the android
以四季豆为例
manifest files or layout files and those
清单文件或布局文件以及那些
files contain they have their own
文件包含它们自己的
structure and they have references to
结构，他们有参考
java code and so on and support and we
java代码等，以及支持，我们
have something called the Dom framework
有一个叫做Dom框架的东西
which makes it very easy to to build
这使得构建非常容易
high level features on top of that so it
最重要的是，它具有高级功能
can build navigation features and
可以建立导航功能并
validation features very easily and to
验证功能非常容易
make sure that your I did you can very
确保你做到了
easily achieve a real level of
轻松达到真实水平
understanding of text a structured by
对文本的理解
the IDE and recently as part of the app
IDE，并且最近作为应用程序的一部分
source integration we have also
源集成，我们也
separated this into UI and on UI parts
将此分为用户界面和用户界面部分
so you shall be like comment line tools
因此，您将像注释行工具一样
its to do something with XML you can do
它可以用XML做一些事情
that without extra dependencies there
那没有额外的依赖
are some other chunks that you may find
您可能会发现其他一些块
useful spell checker images regular
有用的拼写检查图像常规
expressions stuff like that so the
表达式之类的东西，所以
underlying theme of all of that is that
所有这些的根本主题是
the platform is fairly modular and you
该平台是相当模块化的，您
can choose the right set of modules for
可以选择适合的模块集
your specific paths you can choose which
您的具体路径，您可以选择
pieces of functionality you want to
您想要的功能
support your product and you can pull
支持您的产品，您可以拉
the pieces you can take the pieces that
你可以拿的碎片
you need and you can leave out all of
您需要，您可以省去所有
the rest and it's all nice and beyond
其余的一切都很好
the module is viewing the models that we
该模块正在查看我们的模型
have in the community edition we also
在社区版中我们也
have a bunch of plugins that can be
有很多可以
useful for you so I have already
对您有用，所以我已经
mentioned version control integration we
提到版本控制集成我们
have build system integration we have
已经建立了系统集成
test runner integration we have issue
测试运行器集成，我们有问题
tracker integration this may or may not
跟踪器集成，这可能会或可能不会
be appropriate for your product but once
适合您的产品，但是一次
again you may choose to take whatever
再次，你可以选择采取任何
you need
你需要
leave the rest out
其余的留在外面
we have a we have a also fairly new
我们有一个我们也很新
thing that we have as a framer for you
我们为您准备的东西
are building UI designers right now it's
正在建立UI设计师
used by the Android UI designer and by
由Android UI设计者和
the designer that we have objective by
我们有目标的设计师
the detective I designed that we have
我设计的侦探
been building for appcode and if you
正在构建应用程序代码，如果您
want to support a form designer your own
想要支持自己的表单设计者
product you can also build on top of
您还可以在以下产品上构建产品
this framer and get some stuff for free
这个成帧器并免费获得一些东西
having said that I have to mention that
说了我不得不提的是
building a UI designer is still a fair
建立UI设计师仍然是公平的
amount of work and you don't get all of
大量的工作，却没有得到全部
it for free from the platform there is
从平台上免费获得
still quite a lot of stuff that you need
您仍然需要很多东西
to do yourself now let's look at how the
现在做自己，让我们看看如何
internet idea platform compares to some
互联网创意平台相比之下有些
model for example than it sleeps on it
例如模型比它睡在上面
beats RCPS
击败RCPS
so the main thing that needs to be made
所以需要做的主要事情
clear is that we are not building a
很明显，我们不是在建立一个
general-purpose rich client platform we
通用富客户端平台我们
never had this goal and we don't have
从来没有这个目标，我们没有
any any plans to do this in the future
将来有任何计划这样做
and you can probably try to treat our
你可能可以尝试对待我们
code base as this like a general-purpose
这样的通用代码库
UI platform but it's not going to be a
UI平台，但不会成为
very good one so if you just need some
非常好一个，所以如果您只需要一些
companies to build the UI for your
公司为您构建用户界面
application or you will be better off
应用程序，否则您会更好
using netbeans if you like swing or
如果您喜欢swing或使用netbeans
eclipse if you like SWT but on the other
如果您喜欢SWT则会使日食黯然失色
hand if you need to build a concentric
如果需要建立同心圆
tool if you need build to build a tool
工具，如果您需要构建以构建工具
that does something with source code and
这与源代码有关系
then IntelliJ IDEA
然后是IntelliJ IDEA
then internship platform is a great
那么实习平台很棒
choice because it gives you a lot of
选择，因为它给您很多
software free and it gives you a lot of
免费软件，它为您提供了很多
stuff that is going to be very important
将会非常重要的东西
for you and stuff that you take quite a
为你和你需要的东西
lot of time to develop yourself and it's
很多时间发展自己，这是
also in the the IntelliJ IDEA platform
也在IntelliJ IDEA平台中
is also not very perfect for intensive
对于强化训练也不是很完美
applications for example Eclipse has put
Eclipse等应用程序
a lot of effort has invested a lot of
付出了很多努力
effort into building general
努力建设一般
infrastructure for diagramming tools
图表工具的基础架构
like modeling tools and stuff like that
像建模工具之类的东西
and we have some of that intelligent
我们有一些聪明的人
alternate but our framework relies on a
替代，但我们的框架依赖
non open source
非开源
graph library and because of that they
图形库，因此
are not currently people to make this
目前还没有人做到这一点
available as part of IntelliJ IDEA
作为IntelliJ IDEA的一部分提供
community Asian Hornet energy platform
亚洲大黄蜂社区能源平台
it's possible that this will change in
这可能会改变
future parts for now it remains
现在它仍然是将来的零件
available on it for the Centurion it was
可供百夫长使用
not to those people who want to build
不适合那些想要建造的人
product for that platform what kind of
该平台的产品是什么样的
products could there be so first of all
产品首先可以有
obviously yeah we are building IDs and
显然，是的，我们正在构建ID，
you could be ladies as well and I have
你也可以当女士，我有
just listed a few languages for which we
刚刚列出了几种语言，
don't have any immediate plans with our
我们没有任何即时计划
own IDE and for some of them it would be
自己的IDE，对于其中一些人来说
very nice to build it have good tools
构建它非常好，具有良好的工具
out there so there are some probably
在那里，所以大概有一些
things that look weird to you such as I
对你来说很奇怪的事情，例如我
know very long VHDL is like not
知道很长时间VHDL就像不是
something that comes to springs to mind
想到的东西
when you're thinking about languages to
当您在考虑语言时
be the new idea for but still its
成为新想法，但仍然是
programming essentially and as far as I
就我而言，基本上是编程
know the tools that they have right now
知道他们现在拥有的工具
are not very state-of-the-art compared
比较不是最先进的
to business opportunity on out there a
到那里的商业机会
more obvious option is to build framer
更明显的选择是构建成帧器
specific IDs so it's kind of similar to
特定的ID，有点类似于
what this to what the SpringSource does
这对SpringSource的作用
with the speed tool suite as one example
以速度工具套件为例
so the there are a number of such ideas
所以有很多这样的想法
based on eclipse at the moment but there
基于当时的日食，但那里
are a lot of advantages to be had by
有很多优点
building such stuff on top of IntelliJ
在IntelliJ上构建这样的东西
because we have the very good we have
因为我们拥有非常好的
very very good underlying code editing
非常好的基础代码编辑
framework and also started about Dom
框架，也开始介绍Dom
that I was mentioning before it really
我之前提到过的
lets you feel the great product is not
让您感到优质的产品不是
it without investing a whole lot of
它不需要投资很多
stuff time and effort into that another
将时间和精力投入到另一个
thing needs to build is code analysis or
需要构建的是代码分析或
code exploration tools just for this one
仅此一个的代码探索工具
example so we would love if something
例子，所以我们很乐意
like curvature 45 for example was
例如曲率45
integrated with our with our platform
与我们的平台集成
and there there's a lot of other stuff
还有很多其他的东西
that you can build in this
你可以建立在这个
maybe there is a possibility to build
也许有可能建立
something for game development so there
游戏开发的东西，所以那里
is a lot there is a lot of custom
很多很多风俗
program we start not just C++ but also
我们不仅启动C ++程序
stuff like Unreal script or Lua which I
诸如虚幻脚本或Lua之类的东西
have already mention or unity script and
已经提到或统一脚本，并且
maybe there is a big opportunity there
也许那里有很大的机会
building a powerful concentric tool for
建立强大的同心工具
developing that code side of games maybe
开发游戏的代码方面
there is also a business opportunity in
还有一个商机
the ERP area so there's stuff like SAP
ERP区域，所以像SAP这样的东西
and about maybe or something like that
大概是这样的
was a rush for those if you're familiar
如果您熟悉的话，对于那些人来说是急
with some Russian software there is
有一些俄罗斯软件
something called 101's accounting which
叫做101的会计
also has its own programming language
也有自己的编程语言
which does not have any good tools that
没有任何好的工具
maybe someone could build to space on
也许有人可以建立太空
our platform for that that's of course
我们的平台当然是
not all that's just some ideas that came
并非所有这些只是一些想法
to my mind when I was preparing this
在我准备这个的时候
webinar but obviously there's probably a
网络研讨会，但显然可能有一个
lot of other stuff that you cannot come
很多其他你不能来的东西
up with yourself and yes all of those
跟自己在一起，是的，所有这些
are mostly developer tools maybe there
大部分是开发人员工具
is a possibility to build some tools
有可能建立一些工具
which are not targeted on the earth for
这些不是针对地球的
developer space on Italy je a platform
在意大利开发人员空间的平台
something I don't know it's powerful
我不知道它的功能强大
text manipulation tools for example I
文字处理工具，例如我
don't know if a screed writing or stuff
不知道熨平板是不是写东西
like that or interactive fiction or
诸如此类或互动小说或
stuff like that but it's not my really
这样的东西，但这不是我真正的
my task to come up with all the possible
我的任务是想出一切可能
opportunities right here now how is the
现在的机会如何
question of where whether you want to
您是否要去哪里的问题
build up just a bargain or if you want
建立一个讨价还价或如果你想
to build a full-blown product on top of
在上面建立一个成熟的产品
that so first of all in any case you
所以首先无论如何你
have to start with the plugin because
必须从插件开始，因为
essentially what the product is I
本质上是什么产品我
mentioned all what the product is as a
提到所有产品是什么
custom package plug-in with the platform
平台的自定义软件包插件
and before you can do that you can just
在您可以这样做之前，您可以
build a plugin and release it and see
构建一个插件并释放它，看看
how many people use it see if it turns
有多少人使用它，看看它是否变成
out well and then if you decided that
好，然后如果你决定
you liked it you decide to buy that
您喜欢它，因此决定购买
product and once you have a product you
产品，一旦您有了产品，就可以
have the possibility to remove the stuff
有可能删除的东西
that you don't want to add to change the
您不想添加以更改
start if you don't like and essentially
如果你不喜欢就开始
to customize the user experience in any
在任何情况下自定义用户体验
way that you like
你喜欢的方式
and also you get full control over
你也可以完全控制
branding so get to put your own product
品牌推广，让您自己制作产品
name you get to put your logo soul all
命名，将您的徽标灵魂全部
over the place we ask you to specify
在我们要求您指定的地方
that the product is powered by the
产品由
antenna platform and actually the actual
天线平台和实际
license requires you to do this in a
许可证要求您在
specific weight but other than that you
比重，但除此之外
get a lot of control over how the
对如何
product looks in terms of Licensing
产品外观按照许可方式
there is no such big imperative to go
没有那么大的必要性
one way those are there so right now
这些现在在那里的一种方式
there is no restriction on publishing
没有发布限制
commercial plugins to the plug-in
插件的商业插件
repository so you can have plugins that
仓库，所以你可以有插件
ask for license keys essentially and we
本质上要求许可证密钥，我们
don't ask you for any like percentage of
不要问您任何类似的百分比
revenue or anything like that
收入或类似的东西
and the same thing you can do with the
并且您可以使用
product you can build a product that has
您可以构建具有以下特征的产品
a licensees built-in and there is there
内置许可证的人，那里有
are no restrictions to that there was a
没有任何限制
question in the webinar about whether we
网络研讨会中有关我们是否
are going to do something like an app
将要做类似应用程序的事情
store and the answer to this so that you
存储和答案，以便您
can users can get a nice way to
用户能否获得一种不错的方式
distribute commercial stuff easily and
轻松分发商业物品，并且
the answer to that is right now we
答案是现在我们
simply don't see and enough of
根本看不到并且足够
commercial development to make it worse
商业发展使情况更糟
investing into it but in the future
投资但将来
maybe maybe this will become meaningful
也许也许这将变得有意义
let's see how it goes
让我们看看进展如何
so as for licensing as I mentioned the
至于我提到的许可
platform is based on the Apache 2
平台基于Apache 2
license and this puts very few
许可，这很少
restrictions on licensing on direct
直接许可的限制
derivative products you can have them as
衍生产品，您可以将它们作为
open-source you can have them as
开源，您可以将它们作为
commercial any way you like and if you
以您喜欢的任何方式进行商业广告，如果您愿意
if you want to you use some components
如果要使用某些组件
in your browser they're only developed
在您的浏览器中，它们仅是开发的
that are only available as part of the
只能作为
integer your ultimate for example their
整数您的终极，例如他们
diagramming it guides it I already
图解它已经指导了我
mentioned before or I don't know the
之前提到过，否则我不知道
perforce stuff for example it's only
例如perforce的东西
available in ultimate you can talk to us
最终可用，您可以与我们联系
and it's very well possible that we can
而且很有可能我们可以
find a way to license this code to use
找到许可此代码使用的方法
editor so that you would be able to
编辑器，以便您能够
distribute it as part of your product so
作为产品的一部分分发
we are open to discussion on this very
我们非常愿意就此进行讨论
much talk to us and I I'm sure we will
和我们聊很多，我相信我们会
people who would be able to come to a
那些能够来一个
satisfactory solution
满意的解决方案
now having given a high-level overview
现在已经进行了高层概述
let's get a little bit technical and
让我们来一点技术
actually look at the mechanics of
实际看一下
building a product so I will not have to
建立产品，这样我就不必
give a complete walkthrough of this
给出完整的演练
right now because one arm would not be
现在，因为一只手臂不会
enough for that and it probably it will
足以做到这一点，它可能会
bore a lot of you very much
很无聊
so I'll just essentially leave a series
所以我基本上要离开一个系列
of milestones that you will need to go
您需要走的里程碑
through and so that when you actually if
通过，这样当你实际上如果
you actually decide to build a product
您实际上决定制造产品
you will know where to look and you
你会知道在哪里看，你
don't know what questions to ask
不知道要问什么问题
so the key part of every product is
所以每个产品的关键部分是
something called idea dot platform
所谓的想法点平台
prefix and an ideal platform the traffix
前缀和理想平台traffix
is actually a system property that
实际上是一个系统属性
controls which files are loaded by
控制由哪个文件加载
IntelliJ IDEA as industry by the
IntelliJ IDEA被业界视为
intelligent platform as the descriptors
智能平台作为描述符
of the product so there are actually two
产品的数量，所以实际上有两个
main files that specify what the product
指定产品的主文件
Iran actually is and I'm going to talk a
伊朗实际上是，我将谈一谈
bit about them in the next slides but
在下一张幻灯片中介绍一下它们，但
the key thing is that this system
关键是这个系统
property specifies which files are going
属性指定要去的文件
to be loaded and you said this value of
要加载，您说的是
this property in the default VM options
默认VM选项中的此属性
for your product so that it always loads
为您的产品，以便它总是加载
the stuff that you need so the first of
您需要的东西，所以第一个
these files is some so-called plug-in
这些文件是一些所谓的插件
file so the name of this file is ideal
文件，因此此文件的名称是理想的
doctor from the prefix and then plug it
从前缀医生，然后将其插入
on XML and it has exactly the same
在XML上，它具有完全相同的
structure as a regular plug-in XML file
作为常规插件XML文件的结构
that you that you need to write
你需要写的
obviously some of the stuff there does
显然那里有一些东西
not really make sense such as since
像
builds until you build and stuff like
积累，直到你建立和类似的东西
that
那
but their overall structure the list of
但他们的整体结构
components a list of actions list of
组件的动作列表
extensions and extension points it's
扩展和扩展点是
exactly the same as for individual
与个人完全相同
plugins and obviously you don't have to
插件，显然您不必
list all of the components that you want
列出所需的所有组件
to include directly in this file you can
直接包含在此文件中，您可以
include the necessary chance of
包括必要的机会
functionality that you want to have
您想要的功能
access to so all over so they're our own
如此访问，所以它们是我们自己的
files are built essentially is a tree of
文件的构建本质上是一棵树
separate channels that include each
单独的渠道，包括每个
other and you can select the one that
其他，您可以选择一个
you need to have in your product so this
您需要包含在您的产品中，因此
is probably the most basic version of
可能是最基本的版本
the product plug-in file so you just if
产品插件文件，这样您就可以
you are just including the entirety of
你只是包括整个
their IntelliJ IDEA plugin for
他们的IntelliJ IDEA插件
and starting with that is probably the
从那开始可能是
easiest part to get something runny that
最容易得到流鼻涕的东西
looks like a product built on top of the
看起来像是建立在
platform
平台
and of course to look at the source code
当然要看一下源代码
of IntelliJ and look at idea like in dot
的IntelliJ并像点中那样看想法
XML file to get a more realistic example
XML文件以获得更真实的示例
of how this looks like so you see that
看起来如何，所以你看到了
ubi declaring some most of the file
ubi声明了大部分文件
contains of includes of other files so
包含其他文件的包含，因此
includes something called reach platform
包括所谓的到达平台
plug-in debugger and ten power pack
插件调试器和十个电源
annotation gadgets and so on and so
注释小工具等等
forth and then you have the regular list
第四，然后您有常规列表
of components and extension to the
组件和扩展
points and exceptions and stuff like
要点和例外之类的东西
that the second file is the application
第二个文件是应用程序
info file and this file actually is the
信息文件，该文件实际上是
single entry point for all the branding
所有品牌的单一入口点
information that you have in your
您所拥有的信息
product so it specifies a proper product
产品，因此它指定了合适的产品
name all the logos that you use version
命名您使用的所有徽标版本
number build number so on and so forth
编号生成编号依此类推
and normally you your build script
通常你的构建脚本
patches this takes this file from the
修补程序会从
restaurant all and matches it to the
餐厅全部并将其匹配到
correct build number there and this is
正确的内部版本号，这是
like a very simplified example of the
就像一个非常简化的例子
file so I have stripped out most of the
文件，所以我删除了大部分
fields there but you see the important
领域，但您会看到重要的
ones so for like the company name and
这样的公司名称和
the build number and the URLs for the
内部版本号和网址
boundbox image and the splash screen
绑定盒图像和启动屏幕
image you can also look at the file in
图片，您也可以在
the IntelliJ IDEA source code so this is
IntelliJ IDEA源代码，所以这是
like a much more complete stuff so you
喜欢更完整的东西，所以你
see that actually have to specify a lot
看到实际上必须指定很多
of different colors here and the names
这里有不同的颜色和名称
and URLs and stuff like that but the
和网址之类的东西，但是
thing is that all of these depends on
问题是所有这些都取决于
the specific product and you can change
具体产品，您可以更改
all of the stuff and if there is
所有的东西，如果有的话
something that you cannot change then
那你无法改变的东西
it's a bargain you can file it to us and
您可以将其归档给我们，并且
we will fix it
我们将修复它
once you have those two files you have
一旦拥有了这两个文件
to actually build build the product in
实际构建产品
some way
某种方式
and the best way to do this right now is
现在最好的方法是
just to take the bill script that builds
只是拿建立的账单脚本
IntelliJ IDEA Community Edition and
IntelliJ IDEA社区版和
simply to fork it and to make your
简单地将其分叉并使您的
changes to join this into the suite for
更改以将其加入套件
the your own product the script leaves
脚本留下的您自己的产品
and Bill / - distort Gantt in the source
和Bill /-在源代码中扭曲甘特
code of Community Edition and the way it
版的代码及其方式
works is first of all it uses something
作品首先要用一些东西
called GPS which ours which is our
叫做GPS这是我们的
homegrown build system is the same thing
本地构建系统是一回事
that we are right now using inside and
我们现在在内部使用
energy as our external build system and
能源作为我们的外部构建系统，
whatever else you do essentially is it
从本质上讲，您所做的一切是
lets you build unless you build an
除非您构建一个
IntelliJ IDEA product from the command
命令中的IntelliJ IDEA产品
line or from the ID either way so we are
线或从ID中选择一种方式
simply the build script loads the
只需构建脚本加载
product file for the community different
社区的产品档案不同
it builds it it gets a bunch of grass
它建立它得到一堆草
files and then it does something called
文件，然后执行称为
layout which actually takes the class
实际上课的布局
files from the output directory and
输出目录中的文件和
packages them into jar files according
将它们打包成jar文件
to the structure you specify so it takes
到您指定的结构，因此需要
a leader and the plugins director and
领导者和插件主管，以及
puts all each module in its correct
将所有每个模块都放在正确的位置
place and it's actually very nice DSL
的地方，这实际上是非常不错的DSL
that we have also built internally based
我们也在内部建立了
on cat and in a layout of course you
在猫身上，当然在布局上
have the common part which is used for
具有用于
all of the platforms and there are also
所有平台，还有
platform specific parts for Windows
Windows平台特定的部分
Linux and Mac for example the there is a
以Linux和Mac为例，
small number of native code components
少量的本机代码组件
and those components are specific to
这些组件是特定于
each platform and there is something
每个平台都有东西
called for example the bad file make
例如称为坏文件
some distributions he was a very simple
有些分布他很简单
example of a layout script just just cut
刚刚剪切的布局脚本示例
out from our main build script so you
从我们的主要构建脚本中删除，因此您
see that by nesting these do your Mac
嵌套这些即可看到Mac
functions you can define the source for
您可以定义源的函数
directories and then you specify the jar
目录，然后指定jar
files and specify which modules go into
文件并指定将哪些模块放入
each jar file so it's very nice very
每个jar文件非常好
readable DSL and we like it very much
可读的DSL，我们非常喜欢
and yeah the complete complete complete
是的，完整，完整，完整
file is also quite obviously quite a bit
文件也很明显相当多
bigger that's the ultimate one that's
更大的是最终的
not the one
不是那个
still it still uses the same structure
它仍然使用相同的结构
very clean and very readable so a couple
很干净，很可读，所以一对
of other things that I would like to
我想做的其他事情
mention so first of all the windows
首先提到窗户
launcher so previously we used to exe 4G
发射器，所以以前我们曾经执行4G
to build the windows launcher which is a
建立Windows启动器
commercial product now we have our own
现在我们有自己的商品
launcher that is open-source and we have
启动器是开源的，我们有
something called launch of generator
所谓的发电机启动
which matches it to include correct
匹配它以包含正确的
branding and stuff like that
品牌和类似的东西
and there is a function to build it
并且有一个功能来构建它
which is part of our Gans creep set you
这是我们的甘斯（Gans）爬行游戏的一部分
also want to change this and have your
也想改变这个，让你的
own launcher if you are building a
自己的启动器（如果您要构建一个
product on top of IntelliJ platform then
然后将产品放在IntelliJ平台之上
we actually have to build the
我们实际上必须建立
distributions for Windows Mac and Linux
Windows Mac和Linux发行版
and right now we are not giving it as
现在我们不给它
much help for this as we would like to
我们希望为此提供很多帮助
be giving so for example the scripts for
给出例如脚本
publishing installer are not open source
发布安装程序不是开源的
at the moment to be once to open source
目前是一次开源
them and this will happen probably in
他们，这可能会发生在
the coming months but they cannot give
未来几个月，但他们无法付出
any promises unfortunately for the Mac
不幸的是，对于Mac而言，任何承诺
the troupe's ability mg are very much
剧团的能力很强
coupled to our own environment so our
加上我们自己的环境
ability to actually assess Aegis into a
将宙斯盾实际评估为
Mac machine and run the script there to
Mac机器并在其中运行脚本
build the dmg which is actually this
建立实际上是这个的dmg
future self is written in Perl of all
未来的自我写在所有人的Perl中
things and it's not something that we
东西，这不是我们的东西
are looking forward to open sourcing so
期待开源
you need to use your brought your own
您需要使用自己带来的
solutions for Linux is fortunately easy
幸运的是，Linux的解决方案很容易
it's just the dark a seed file and it's
这只是黑暗的种子文件，它是
very easy to build and finally if you go
非常容易构建，如果可以的话
if you're if you have everything working
如果您一切正常
correctly and with you have a product
正确并且与您有产品
and actually you start distributing it
实际上你开始分发它
the results a number of things that you
结果很多事情，你
have to think about in the server side
必须在服务器端考虑
so you have to think about whether they
所以你要考虑他们是否
accept where the exception imports go
接受异常导入的位置
how to provide automatic updates and
如何提供自动更新以及
patches for this part where you like you
您喜欢的部分的补丁
can actually use a lot of our stuff so
实际上可以使用很多东西，所以
the batch building facade is part of the
批处理建筑立面是
community different source code and the
社区不同的源代码和
updates file is very simple XML file
更新文件是非常简单的XML文件
that you just have to put somewhere on
你只需要放在某个地方
your server and to tell the URL specify
您的服务器并告诉URL指定
the URL in the application info file so
应用程序信息文件中的URL，因此
it's very easy to support that
支持它很容易
you probably want to figure out
你可能想弄清楚
something about the plug-in repository
有关插件存储库的一些信息
either use ours as then Android studio
要么使用我们的Android Studio
does or somehow build your own or
是否或以某种方式建立自己的
something that you have to think about
您必须考虑的事情
where the user statistics go whether you
用户统计信息流向何处
want to share them with us or if you
想与我们分享它们，或者如果您
want to have yourself stuff like that
想拥有自己的东西
and once again the application info file
再次是应用程序信息文件
is where you can customize all of the
您可以在其中自定义所有
stuff that is that every URL that the
就是每个网址
product accesses from me from it is
来自我的产品访问权是
customizable to adapt to get influenced
可定制以适应影响
we can put all that stuff on your
我们可以将所有这些东西放到您的
servers and not reference of the
服务器，而不是参考
generate stuff at all so finally one
产生东西，所以最后一个
more one last question that we promised
我们答应的最后一个问题
to answer how to contribute to the
回答如何为
IntelliJ IDEA platform it's actually
实际上是IntelliJ IDEA平台
very easy just go to you just sign this
非常容易，只需去签名即可
yearly the contributor License Agreement
年度贡献者许可协议
send it to us by email and then you just
通过电子邮件发送给我们，然后您就可以
go to github and send us a pool request
转到github并向我们发送池请求
and if when you build your product if
如果您在构建产品时
you run into some limitation of the
你遇到了一些限制
platform some API which is missing and
平台缺少一些API，
not available in the product you can
您可以在产品中找不到
always add this and send us it will
始终添加并发送给我们
request for to disinter at the core
要求分离的核心
platform and we try to be good in
平台，我们会努力做到
reviewing that will regress and
审查将退步和
including them into the product event
将它们纳入产品活动
obviously you need to provide some
显然，您需要提供一些
motivation why you want this and why
动机为什么你想要这个，为什么
this is the best approach that you can
这是最好的方法
take but all in all yeah just those it
拿走，但总的来说，就是那些
happen that's it so that was what I
就是这样，这就是我
wanted to tell you today and now I'm
想今天告诉你，现在我
going we should have plenty of time for
我们应该有足够的时间
discussion and
讨论和
and so let's see a switch to the
因此，让我们看看切换到
questions and answer part okay I'm sorry
问题和答案部分还可以，对不起
yeah thank you yeah okay yeah so we've
是的，谢谢你，是的，所以我们
received a number of questions as part
收到了一些问题
of the river webinar registration I
网络研讨会注册我
guess we'll start with answering those
猜测我们将从回答这些问题开始
and then we can take questions from the
然后我们可以从
audience if there are Thank You Dimitri
听众是否有谢谢迪米特里
for your presentation right now I'm
现在为您的演讲我
looking through the list Oh for
在列表中寻找哦
questions we got from people who set up
我们从建立人那里得到的问题
the web now some of them are us words in
网络上现在有些是我们的话
your voice but we have some interesting
您的声音，但我们有一些有趣的地方
ones so a question from you Ruby fan so
那些是您的问题Ruby粉丝如此
is it possible to use any other non je
是否可以使用任何其他非je
languages for plugins or product for
插件或产品的语言
intuitive platform right now you have to
直观的平台，现在您必须
use a language that compiles to Chavez
使用编译为查韦斯语的语言
so you can use a Java or cousin or Scala
因此您可以使用Java或表兄弟或Scala
or maybe clover
或三叶草
or maybe something or maybe groovy but
或某些东西或古怪但
with Ruby it's going to be interesting
使用Ruby会很有趣
so it may be possible to use like
所以有可能像
compiled JRuby code to build a product
编译JRuby代码以构建产品
but it's not something that we are doing
但这不是我们正在做的事情
internally yet so it's essentially
在内部，所以本质上
thanks heroes another question you
谢谢英雄们另一个问题你
mentioned that but maybe you could
提到，但也许你可以
provide more details
提供更多细节
is it possible right right now to to
现在有可能
deliver commercial products on top of
在...之上提供商业产品
IntelliJ platform absolutely yes it's
IntelliJ平台绝对是
possible
可能
and the there are no restrictions to
而且没有任何限制
doing that
那样做
and if you do it on top of wagons API is
如果您在旅行车API之上执行此操作，
it any other any plans for making a kind
还有其他任何一种计划
of App Store for plugins yeah as I
的App Store的插件不错，就像我一样
mentioned this really depends on the
提到这真的取决于
level of interest that we get so for now
我们目前的兴趣水平
we don't have many commercial plugins
我们没有很多商业插件
and if we do have them we probably are
如果我们有它们，我们可能是
going to build such an app store but for
打算建立这样的应用程序商店，但对于
now it's not not in our near-term plans
现在不是我们的近期计划
you
您
okay some users are also curious if
好吧，一些用户也好奇
there are any policy on protection of
有任何保护
fossil rights and offshore party
化石权与离岸党
products so how does Goodwin's plan to
产品，那么古德温的计划如何
proceed with possibly commercial sub
继续进行可能的商业订购
party plugins that implement the
实现
implements free features eligible for
实现符合条件的免费功能
inclusion into core functionality of
纳入核心功能
your products so things like that so the
您的产品之类的东西
answer to this is the Ashley we hate
对此的答案是我们讨厌的阿什利
doing complicate work so if there is a
做复杂的工作，所以如果有
good plugin that that's something that
好的插件就是
we want to do in our product then first
我们首先要在我们的产品中做
of all we want to talk to the developer
我们要与开发人员交谈的所有内容
of the plug-in and find out if there is
的插件，并找出是否存在
any possibility to use their code and
使用他们的代码的任何可能性
actually there are quite a few plugins
其实有很多插件
that we are shipping as part of the
我们将其作为
internet ID distribution which were
互联网ID分配
originally peels has open source plugins
最初的Pepes具有开源插件
by third-party developers and obviously
由第三方开发商开发，显然
if every time we ask for permission and
如果每次我们都请求许可并
every time we come to some terms that
每次我们达成一些条件
are agreeable to those parties and keep
同意这些当事人并保持
the code if there is a commercial
代码，如果有商业广告
plug-in there is also opportunity we are
插件我们也有机会
also willing to either simply point out
也愿意指出
people to the existing solution and
人们使用现有的解决方案
leave it as a separate product or if we
保留为单独的产品，或者
really want this to have to be bundled
真的希望这个必须捆绑在一起
then we will discuss the possibility of
然后我们将讨论
licensing the existing commercial
许可现有的商业广告
product so that we could include this as
产品，以便我们可以将其作为
it is part of our code base
它是我们代码库的一部分
I'm sinks and the next one is more
我沉了，下一个更多
technical it's about a visual designer
技术是关于视觉设计师的
how rich has API for visual designer is
视觉设计师的API有多丰富
in IntelliJ platform and can be used in
可以在IntelliJ平台中使用
only an Ultimate Edition or in IntelliJ
仅终极版或IntelliJ
platform as well so the visual designer
平台以及视觉设计师
is part of their community different
是他们社区的一部分
source code is not part of ultimate as
源代码不是最终的一部分，因为
for assurance I guess you can just look
为了保证我想你可以看看
at it and see what it does and it
在它，看看它做什么和它
basically provides you with the
基本上为您提供
foundation for building a designer but
建立设计师的基础，但是
the designer itself it's not something
设计师本身不是什么
if you have built you have to okay and
如果您已经建造好了，就必须
as a user asks if there are any
如用户询问是否有任何
accessibility features in the platform
平台中的辅助功能
other than what's being provides by
除了所提供的
default no so we don't have any specific
默认值否，所以我们没有任何特定的
for accessibility you know and another
您知道的可及性
question is about any more quality
问题是关于更多质量
metric tools for plug-in developers they
插件开发人员的公制工具
can use actually the best tool that we
可以实际使用我们最好的工具
can recommend here is the tools that we
可以推荐这里是我们所使用的工具
are using yourself ourselves which is
在使用自己
your kid your kid our profiler it gives
你的孩子你的孩子我们的分析器
a very good overview of performance and
很好的性能概述
memory of users of a java application
Java应用程序用户的内存
and you can use it to explore what
你可以用它来探索
operations are taking on in your plugin
操作正在您的插件中进行
and how much memory to use and so on
以及要使用多少内存等等
okay and one more question on how to
好吧，还有一个关于如何
maybe the best way to deal with change
也许是应对变化的最好方法
in API so some users mentioned that they
在API中，因此一些用户提到他们
encountered problems with after some
经过一些遇到问题
major change in API what was the best
API的重大变化是什么才是最好的
way to do with that problem
解决这个问题的方法
well actually it's one part we're
嗯，这实际上是我们的一部分
building a product actually saves you a
开发产品实际上可以节省您
lot of pain because you you are
很痛苦，因为你
depending you are depending on a
取决于你取决于
specific version of the platform you
您平台的特定版本
choose which version is that is that you
选择那是你的哪个版本
choose my to upgrade to a newer one and
选择我升级到较新的
there is never like an expand and
从来没有像扩大和
expected breakage
预期破损
the reason fortunately if you are
幸运的是，如果你是
building a plugin unfortunately you do
不幸的是，您构建了一个插件
have to deal with API changes and we try
必须处理API更改，我们尝试
to minimize them but in order to be able
最小化它们，但是为了能够
to evolve the platform in the direction
向方向发展平台
that we want to solve it we simply have
我们想要解决它，我们只需
to break the API so in order to
破坏API，以便
modularize it and break the dependencies
对其进行模块化并打破依赖关系
that are inappropriate and all of these
那是不合适的，所有这些
broad breadth of usage with up source in
来源广泛，使用范围广
the concept pilot would not be possible
概念试点将不可能
at all if we had to preserve a
如果我们必须保留一个
compatibility between versions
版本之间的兼容性
and probably the best one from day four
可能是第四天最好的
he asks about picture vlogging so yeah
他问有关图片博客的问题，是的
I'm reading yeah actually is a question
我在读yeah实际上是一个问题
is what peach farm does represent is it
桃园到底代表什么
a single plug-in product yeah so with
单一的插件产品
the story with my charm is that so yeah
我有魅力的故事是这样
actually you can build a plugin that
其实你可以建立一个插件
runs both both with IntelliJ and the
同时与IntelliJ和
Python value and also with by charm and
Python的价值以及魅力和
obviously bar charm is a commercial
显然酒吧的魅力是商业性的
products you if you want to build your
产品，如果您想建立自己的
own product on top of my charm then you
在我的魅力之上拥有自己的产品，然后你
need to come with the need to discuss
需要与需要讨论
device anything with us because so you
向我们提供任何设备，因为这样您
need essentially to become a reseller of
本质上需要成为经销商
pycharm something like that which is
pycharm是这样的
possible but it's not as easy as it is
可能，但并非如此简单
with the source stuff but technically
与源的东西，但技术上
yes you can build a plug-in that works
是的，您可以构建一个可以正常工作的插件
for works for by charming users by the
用于由
specific api's
特定的api
so any more questions yes
所以还有其他问题吗
that's all what we have so far okay then
那就是我们到目前为止所有的一切
if no one has any more questions then
如果没有人有其他问题，那么
thank you for your attention and if you
谢谢您的关注，如果您
have any questions technical or non
有技术或非问题
technical or business related please
请与技术或业务相关
feel free to contact me directly so why
请随时直接与我联系，为什么
it just rains that come come or just
只是下雨而已
follow me on Twitter or and I will be I
在Twitter上关注我，否则我将成为我
will be happy to help you with any like
会很乐意帮助您
technical or marketing or business
技术或营销或业务
issues or I will put you in touch with
问题，否则我会与您联系
the right people to help you with the
合适的人来帮助您
company so thanks everyone we will have
公司，谢谢大家，我们将有
the reporting up sorry adjust to it okay
报告了抱歉，请调整一下
go ahead yeah just to add a few comments
继续，是的，只是添加一些评论
you can find more information on
您可以在以下找到更多信息
IntelliJ platform on its home page G
IntelliJ平台首页G
brains dot o org you can also see the
大脑点组织，你也可以看到
source code of frontage a community
社区正面的源代码
edition on github so all sources are
版本在github上，所以所有来源都是
available and for plug-in development
可用并用于插件开发
you can go to our conference space and
您可以去我们的会议空间
find the documentation on all steps how
查找所有步骤的文档
to draw plugins and if you encounter any
绘制插件，如果遇到任何问题
question you you can answer yourself you
问题，你可以回答自己你
can ask it on developer community forum
可以在开发者社区论坛上提问
so and our developers monitor these
因此，我们的开发人员会监控这些
these questions and we'll be happy to
这些问题，我们很乐意
help you with these questions
帮助您解决这些问题
so yes it's all thank you for your
所以是的，这一切都感谢你的
attending for our Twitter account and if
参加我们的Twitter帐户，如果
you have any questions on partnership
您对合伙有任何疑问
please contact contacted me tree or
请联系与我联系的树或
Brian now with this email address and we
Brian现在有了这个电子邮件地址，我们
will take Oh No
会带哦不
from this session and will publish it
从本届会议开始，并将其发布
within a week after today yeah thank you
在今天之后的一个星期内，是的，谢谢
okay thank you
好的谢谢